Our orders are heavily delayed.  Could they have forgotten
?
They might be.
Pardon.  We want three iselaks.
One is lactose-flavored almond, the
other is oat milk.
Why aren't you taking notes?
We'll make them all with the same milk.
Everyone working here is very friendly.
The manager is here.
Pardon.  Can we share this between the two of us
?
You can share it with up to 6 people if you like.  What do I care?
Pardon.  Could you take a picture of us?
Of course.  Let me finish the dream of this table.
I am coming.
Which one would you eat?
Staff meal.  Free.
What is the chef's specialty?
Whichever one is left more today.  Oh,
sorry, I didn't like this.
Of course you wouldn't like it.  Don't mention caviar.
I brought olive paste.
You don't even know what caviar is.  Is Haver at your mother's house too
?  Get up and go, square.
Pardon.  Can I get the Wi-Fi password
?
So, for the first time in 40 years, you've met up with your friends
.  Sit down and chat.
What are you going to do with the Wi-Fi password?   Will you
tell me?
This is the password.  With 40 digits.   I'm
sorry, we've tired you out a lot
today.
If you want to make amends, the door is right over there.
Good luck.  We had run out of toilet paper.   If you
cover the toilet seat with tissues every time you use the restroom, it'll be over.  Get out of here
.  We can't do without sitting down.  House.